(悟)＜あの現象を
俺は リバイバルと呼んでいる＞
I call the phenomenon "Revival."
＜だいたい
１分から５分くらい前に戻って
I usually go back
between one and five minutes,
同じ光景を見る＞
where everything is the same as before.
＜決まって
何か悪いことが起こる直前だ＞
It's always right before
something bad happens.
＜結果 何度となく
トラブルを回避してきた＞
As a result, I've kept trouble
from happening again and again.
(佐知子)おかえり 悟｡
(悟)母さん…｡
Welcome home, Satoru.
Mom...
(警察官)藤沼 悟さんですか？➡ 署で
事情を 聴かせていただきたいんですが｡
Are you Satoru Fujinuma?
I need to take you down to the station...
Ice Hockey Club 1988 National Champions
ERASED
Did you see "Mask Man"?
It said next week's the last episode!
｢マスクマン｣見た？次最終回だって｡
(児童)あ～
俺 ｢ブラック｣ 見んの忘れた！
I forgot to watch "Black"!
(悟)《昭和63年 ２月15日？》
1988...
February 15th
February 15th?
≪(戸の開閉音)
(八代)おはよう みんな！
(児童たち)おはようございます！
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning!
(八代)どうした？ 悟｡ 早く
席に着け｡ (悟)えっ？ あっ はい｡
What's wrong, Satoru? Take your seat.
Right.
(悟)《席 どこだ？》
Where do I sit?
(悟)あっ｡
寝ぼけてんの？ 藤沼｡ えっ？ そこ 雛月の席だべ｡ あっ｡
Are you still half-asleep, Fujinuma?
That's Hinazuki's desk.
(八代)月曜日…｡
加代は 今週も遅刻か｡
Monday. Kayo's late this week, too...
(美里)
藤沼って 加代のこと好きなの？
Are you in love with Kayo, Fujinuma?
えっ？
フッ｡
You're both weird. Birds of a feather.
変わり者同士 お似合いだべさ｡
(八代)出席を取るぞ｡
I'm taking attendance.
- Asuna.
- Here.
《これは 現実なのか…》
Is this real?
- Abiko.
- Here.
《何で
こんな所に来ちまったんだ？》
Why did I end up here?
- Abe.
- Here.
- Ikuta.
(児童)はい｡
《どういうことだよ？
18年も前だぞ》
What's the meaning of this?
It's 18 years ago...
(児童)
ドラクエⅢ どこまで いった？
How far have you gotten
with "Dragon Quest III"?
(児童)俺 レベル15｡
(児童)えっ!? おっせえ！
Level 15!
That's all?!
(児童)嘘！ ホントは レベル25｡
(児童)嘘つけ！
Just kidding. Really level 25.
Liar!
(ケンヤ)悟 どうした？
ちょっと 頭 痛いから 保健室｡
Satoru, what's wrong?
I've got a headache,
so I'm going to the nurse's office.
(ケンヤ)ランドセル 持ってか？
With your backpack?
まあ いいや｡
先生には 言っといてやるよ｡
Whatever.
I'll let the teacher know.
What the hell is going on?
《いったい 何が？
リバイバルなのか？》
Is it Revival?
《何で こんな…｡
訳 分かんねえ》
Why is it happening like this?
I don't understand.
あっ…｡
母さん！
Mom!
♬～
FUJINUMA
(チャイム)
≪(足音)
こ… こんにちは！
(女性)ごめんね！ お待たせ！
H-Hello!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
《知らねえやつかよ》
A stranger, huh?
≪(足をぶつける音)
《そうか…｡ 仕事 行ってるよな》
That's right.
She'd be at work.
♬～
《母さん…》
Mom...
≪(ドアの開く音)
うん？
ただいま｡
あっ…｡
I'm back.
母さん…｡
母さん？
Ma...
"Ma"?
えっ？
お… お母さんって言ったでしょ？
I said "Mom."
変な子ね｡
My son is weird.
What do you want,
hamburger or meatballs?
ハンバーグとミートボール
どっちさ 食べたい？
ハ… ハンバーグ｡
H-Hamburger...
♬～
Almost done.
もう少し 待ってね｡
うん｡
フフフッ｡
(佐知子)朝さ 笛がないとか 大騒ぎして
ケンカしたのにさもう忘れたみたい｡
Even after that argument we had this morning
about you not having the recorder,
it looks like you still forgot it.
ごめんなさい お母さん｡
I'm sorry, Mom.
泣かなくてもいいべさ｡
えっ？
It's not worth crying about.
フフッ｡
《俺にも
こんな時間があったんだ》
We had times like this, too.
《忘れていた？
いや 気付かなかったんだ》
Had I forgotten?
No. I just didn't realize it then.
《何げなく過ごしていた
俺が 失ってしまった時間》
I let it slip by
without even thinking about it.
Time that I lost...
This is Revival after all.
《やっぱり
これは リバイバルだ》
《これは チャンスなんだ》
This is a chance.
《この時間を失ってたまるか》
And no way am I gonna lose this time.
お母さん｡
うん？
Mom...
おいしいよ｡ ありがとう｡
なしたの？ 悟｡
This is really good. Thank you.
What's the matter, Satoru?
ごちそうさま｡
(佐知子)はーい｡
Thank you for dinner.
You're welcome.
(児童)おはよう！
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Good morning!
Morning!
《俺は このまま
18年間を やり直すのか？》
Am I supposed to fix the next 18 years?
(オサム)おはよう 悟！
お… おっす！ オサム！
Morning, Satoru!
Hey, Osamu!
《これが リバイバルなら
ここにいるのは 偶然じゃない》
If this is Revival, then it's
no coincidence that I'm here.
《きっと
何か悪いことを防ぐためだ》
It has to be to prevent
something bad from happening.
《つまり
ここが 母さんを救う起点？》
In other words, is this
the starting point for saving Mom?
Ice Hockey Club 1988 National Champions
《でも 何で この時代なんだ｡
違和感なんて どこにも…》
But why this time period?
Nothing feels wrong here.
《うん？》
うん？
《雛月 加代｡
確か 母親と２人暮らし》
Kayo Hinazuki...
She lived with her mother, as I recall.
(八代)よっ｡
(児童たち)うわぁ｡ すげえ｡
Awesome...
That's perfect.
《うん？ 打撲傷？》
A bruise?
(オサム)やっぱ このグループ 変わってるよな｡
誰とも ドラクエの話 できないんだもん｡
There's something wrong with this group.
Not one of you guys can chew
the fat about "Dragon Quest."
Y-Yeah...
う… うーん｡ だってヒロはフｧイフｧンだしカズは シューティングしかやんないし｡
I mean, Hiro is a "Final Fantasy" fan,
and Kazu only plays shooting games...
《ヒロ…｡ カズ…｡
思い出してきた》
Hiro...
Kazu...
Now I remember.
悟なんて
ファミコン 持ってないべや｡
And you don't have a Nintendo, Satoru.
《そうだっけか》
Is that right?
でも オサム ドラクエ仲間とは
ドラクエの話しかできないだろ？
But fellow "Dragon Quest" fans can only
talk about "Dragon Quest," right, Osamu?
俺は 趣味が ばらばらな
このﾒﾝﾊﾞｰだから いいと思ってるよ｡
I like this group because
everyone's got different interests.
《ケンヤ｡ 昔 思ってたとおり
頭のいいやつだ》
Kenya...
He always was the smart one.
ところでさ 悟一つ 聞いていいか？
えっ？ 何？
By the way, Satoru,
can I ask you something?
What is it?
(ケンヤ)お前雛月のこと 好きなの？ えっ!?
Do you like Hinazuki?
えっ!?
You were staring at her
the whole time in class.
授業中 ずっと見てたろ｡
(ヒロミ)えっ そうなの？
Really?!
あっ そうそう！ 朝も突っ立って
雛月のこと ずっと見てたべさ！
That's right!
This morning too, he was just
standing there, gazing at her!
(カズ)何だ 悟！ それなら
何で 俺たちに相談しねえのよ！
Come on, Satoru!
Why didn't you come to us for advice?
俺に 任せれや！
なっ…｡
Leave it to me!
Wha...
(カズ)俺が 雛月と話せるように
しちゃるからよ！
I'll make it so you can talk to Hinazuki!
こ… 声が大きいよ｡
K-Keep your voice down.
(カズ)うん？
U-Um...
あ… あの 好きっていうか
ちょっと気になってる｡
It's not that I "like" her.
More like she's kind of on my mind.
わ～っ 言った！
(ヒロミ)悟君 大胆！
Listen to him!
Satoru, you've got guts!
よっしゃ！ よく言った！
放課後に会えるよう
All right! Well said!
I'll arrange it so you can
see her after school!
俺が 段取りしちゃる！
あっ！
(雛月)バカなの？
《ど直球だな！》
Are you an idiot?
She cut right to the chase.
Is that how you greet someone?!
第一声が それかよ！
《声に出てた…》
I said that out loud.
《カズのやつ 何のひねりもなく
俺が好きだって 伝えやがったな》
That Kazu...
I bet he told her flat
out that I had a crush on her.
あ… あのさ
友達になれないかなって思って｡
L-Look...
I thought maybe we could be friends.
帰る方向も 一緒だしさ｡
After all, we go home the same way.
私なんかの どこを見て
そんなこと言ってるの？
Why would you say that
to me of all people?
《めんどくせえ がきだな…》
This brat is a pain in the ass.
でも 何か 少し分かる｡
But I understand a little bit.
藤沼ってさ
私と一緒で 偽者だから｡
You and I are both fakes, Fujinuma.
《何だ こいつ…｡
何を言ってる》
What the hell?
What's she talking about?
昨日 走って帰る藤沼 見たよ｡
えっ？
I saw you run home yesterday, Fujinuma.
母親って そんなに大切なもの？
Is your mother that precious to you?
うん！
そう｡
Yeah.
Oh.
ちょっ… 雛月！
待ってよ！
Hey... Hinazuki!
Wait!
お前と 友達になりたいんだ！
友達？
I wanna be friends!
Friends?
じゃあ
私のために 人を殺せる？
Then would you kill someone for my sake?
《僕なら
助けられたはずなのに！》
I could've saved her!
《殺される雛月には
事件以前から 何かが起きている》
Something was happening with Hinazuki
even before she was murdered.
《この大きな違和感を解決すれば
もしかしたら…》
If I can figure it out in time, maybe...
Episode 2
Palm of the Hand
You and I are both fakes, Fujinuma.
(雛月)《藤沼ってさ
私と一緒で 偽者だから》
《俺の中身が 本物じゃないと
見抜いたわけじゃない》
I'm sure she didn't mean it like she saw
the adult me posing as my kid self.
《まあ 手探り状態で
過ごしていたのは 確かだけど》
True, I was playing it by ear there,
《それは
小学生だったころも同じだ》
but I was the same way
the first time around in elementary school.
《周りと うまく付き合うために
I played a version of myself
to get along well with people around me.
こう ありたいという自分を
演じていた》
(白鳥)
《恥ずかしがらず 勇気を持って》
Without being embarrassed,
but with courage.
《この狭い社会の中で
自分が 適応していくためだ》
It was so I could fit in
with this narrow microcosm.
Sorry about that!
What, did you take a dump?
No!
It took you long enough!
《きっと それを見抜かれている》
That's what she must have seen through.
I thought you fell in!
You must've filled the bowl!
《｢私と一緒｣と言った雛月も
おそらく…》
She said, "You and are I both fakes."
Maybe Hinazuki meant...
熱いね 悟！
You're really hot for her, huh, Satoru?
それで 雛月とは どうだったんだ？
ちゃんと 一緒に帰るべって言えたか？
Speaking of which,
how'd it go with Hinazuki?
Were you able to say,
"Let's walk home together"?
あっ… いや
まだ 少し 話しただけだから｡
No.
We just talked a bit.
(オサム)話したって ２人で？
うん…｡
The two of you talked?
Yeah.
おお！ そりゃ 脈ありってことだべ！
雛月が 二人っきりで話すなんてよ！
That means you've got a chance!
You and Hinazuki talked alone!
Then should I give her
another message on your behalf?
《うぜえ…｡
どう扱えばいいんだ こいつら》
Annoying.
This is so exciting!
How should I deal with these guys?
Quit poking fun, everyone.
ちゃかすなよ みんな｡ 焦って
台無しになったら どうすんだよ｡
What are you going to do if your
overeagerness blows it for him?
(カズ)そうだな…｡
Good point.
Yeah.
《まっ
意味は 曲がったままだけどな》
We're on different pages
here, but oh, well...
(ケンヤ)悟｡
Satoru...
６年になってもクラス替えは
ないんだしさ大事に いけよ｡ うん｡
Even when we're sixth graders,
the class won't change,
so be careful.
I will.
[ﾏｲｸ](ｱﾅｳﾝｽ)
皆さん 下校の時刻と…｡
February 17th
School is out, everyone.
《そういえば
雛月がいなくなるのは いつだ？》
Come to think of it,
when did Hinazuki disappear?
I don't have much time...
Students who are still in the building,
please turn off the lights and close the windows.
《あまり 時間は…》
≪(オサム)悟！ 帰ろうよ！
Satoru, let's go!
Let's all be careful of cars
on the way home.
う… うん｡
R-Right.
(オサム)あれ？
Huh?
悟 こないだ マクレガーの手袋
買ったんじゃなかったっけ？
Satoru, didn't you just
buy McGregor gloves?
《あっ…
そういや そんなの持ってたな》
Now that he mentions it,
I did have those.
どっかに 忘れてきたのかな…｡
Maybe I left them somewhere?
(オサム)ああ そんじゃ
きっと アジトじゃない？
Probably at the hideout.
あっ…｡ みんな
ちょっと アジト 寄ってかない？
You guys wanna stop by the hideout?
何 言ってんの？
What are you talking about?
雪が降って すぐは 足跡が残るから
行かないって 決まりだべさ｡
We already decided
not to go when it snows
because footprints
are left behind, remember?
そ… そうだっけ？
ア… アハハッ｡
D-Did we?
(カズ)したっけ！
(オサム)また あした！
- See you tomorrow!
- See you!
- Yeah!
(ケンヤ)おう！
(悟･ヒロミ)したっけ！
See you!
ケンヤ！ うん？ さっきはありがと｡ 正直周りで
わいわいやられると調子 狂っちゃう…｡
Kenya!
Thanks for before.
It drove me nuts when they
were making a big thing out of it.
そりゃ そうだろ｡
まあ 気にすんなよ｡
Well, of course.
But don't let it bother you.
悟｡
俺はさ
Satoru, listen...
お前が 雛月を気にしていることが何だか
すごく大事なことのように 思えるんだ｡
For some reason, I think
it's really important
that you have your mind on Hinazuki.
もしかしたら
余計なことかもしれないけど
This may be stepping over the line,
何でも 相談してくれないか？
but you can talk to me about anything.
きっと みんなも
悟に 協力したいと思ってる｡
I think all of us want to help you, Satoru.
うん｡ ありがとう｡
Yeah. Thanks.
みんなに
悪気がないのも分かってる｡
I know they don't have any ill will.
カズのおかげで
雛月と話すこと できたし｡
Thanks to Kazu, I was able to talk
to Hinazuki in the first place.
で 実際 どうだった？
えっ？
So how did it really go?
雛月｡
あっ ああ…｡
With Hinazuki.
話 できたの？
Did you talk to her?
うん｡ ちょっとだけ
本音で話してくれたと思う｡
Yeah. A little.
And I think she was being honest with me.
そうか｡
ところでさ 悟
I see.
By the way, Satoru,
recently have you...
最近 お前…｡
文集 読んだ？
えっ？ あっ いや 読んでないよ｡
...read the student
composition collection?
N-No, I haven't read it.
意外と面白いからさ
今度 読んでみなよ｡
It's actually pretty interesting.
Read it when you get a chance.
したっけ｡ また あした｡
したっけ｡
Well, see you tomorrow.
See you!
5th Year, Class 4
Student Composition Collection
BIG WAVE SMALL WAVE
《ケンヤは たぶん雛月の作文のことを 面白いと言ったんだ》
I think Kenya was hinting
that Hinazuki's essay was interesting.
(雛月)｢私だけがいない街
雛月 加代｣
"The Town Without Me,"
by Kayo Hinazuki.
｢今より もっと大きくなって一人で
どこへでも 行けるようになったら
When I get bigger, big enough
to go somewhere by myself,
遠い国に行ってみたい｡
遠い島に行ってみたい｣
I want to go to a land that's far away.
I want to go to a faraway island.
｢誰もいない島に行ってみたい｣
I want to go to an island
that has no people.
｢つらいことも 悲しいこともない
島に行ってみたい｣
I want to go to an island
that has no pain or sadness.
｢島には 大人も子供も クラスメートも
先生もお母さんもいない｣
There are no adults, children, classmates,
teachers or my mom on that island.
｢その島で 私は
登りたいときに 木に登り
On that island, I can climb
a tree when I want to climb,
swim in the sea when I want to swim,
泳ぎたいときに 海で泳ぎ
眠りたいときに 眠る｣
and sleep when I want to sleep.
｢その島で 私は私だけがいなくなった街のことを 考える｣
On the island, I think about
the town that I left behind.
｢子供は
いつものように 学校に行く｣
Kids go to school,
as if nothing has changed.
｢大人は
いつものように 会社に行く｣
Adults go to the office,
as if nothing has changed.
｢お母さんは
いつものように ご飯を食べる｣
Mom eats, as if nothing has changed.
｢私は 私だけがいない街のことを
考えると 気持ちが軽くなる｣
When I think about the town
without me, I feel a sense of relief.
｢遠く 遠くへ行きたい｣
I want to go far, far away.
《雛月の作文は
紛れもなく ＳＯＳだ》
Hinazuki's essay is an SOS,
no doubt about it.
≪(ドアの開く音)
≪(佐知子)ただいま｡
I'm home!
いただきます｡
うん？
Thank you for this meal.
《たぶん ケンヤは
俺が 恋愛感情なんかじゃなく
Maybe Kenya thinks I don't have
a romantic interest in Hinazuki,
文集を読んで 雛月に
関心を持ったと思っている》
but I am concerned about her
after reading her essay.
お母さん｡
何？
Mom...
Yes?
誕生日さ 友達 呼んで
パーティー やっていい？
For my birthday, can I invite
my friends here for a party?
う… うん いいよ｡
Sure.
でも このうちじゃ
大勢は 入れないべさ｡
But not many people can fit in here.
大丈夫｡ ５人くらい｡
That's okay.
I'm thinking about five people.
あんたが
そんなこと言うの 初めてだね｡
This is the first time
you've ever talked about a party.
おっきいケーキ 買うべか？
うん｡ ありがとう｡
Shall I buy a big cake?
Yeah. Thank you!
《俺が 今 なすべきことは
雛月に もっと踏み込むことだ》
What I need to do right now...
is get to know Hinazuki better.
《俺が 過去にやらなかった
アクションを起こす》
I didn't do anything the first time around,
but now I'm going to take action.
《それによって 雛月の行動を変えてこの先
俺の周りで起こる事件を 回避する》
By doing that, I'll change
Hinazuki's behavior
and avoid the crime that would
otherwise occur around me soon.
《それを
ずっと 繰り返していけば…》
If I keep doing that...
≪(佐知子)悟 起きてる？
Satoru, are you awake?
５人って
あんた 彼女でも できた？
Five people...
Do you have a girlfriend?
何だ｡ 寝てるの？
《妖怪め》
Oh. Are you sleeping?
Yokai...
I just remembered something.
《そういや 思い出した》
《俺は このおふくろの
サトリみたいな観察眼が嫌で
I never showed Mom my essay
文集 見せなかったんだ》
because I couldn't stand
the gaze of her all-seeing eye.
《俺は 何 書いたんだっけ？》
But what did I write about again?
(チャイム)
All right! I'm gonna play
"Dragon Quest" when I get home!
(児童)
よーし｡ 帰って ドラクエやろう！
Me too!
(児童)俺も！
(カズ)また 雪か｡アジト 行けねえな｡ (オサム)あっ｡
Snowing again?
Then we can't go to the hideout.
悟｡
雛月 帰っちゃうよ｡ いいの？
Satoru, Hinazuki is leaving.
You don't mind?
オサム｡
いいんだ ケンヤ｡
Osamu...
It's okay, Kenya.
I'll catch up with her.
追っ掛けるから｡
オサム ありがとう｡ したっけ！
Thanks, Osamu.
したっけ！
(カズ)したっけ！
See you!
- See you!
おお…｡
(ヒロミ)悟君 大胆だな～｡
Satoru really has guts!
《走らなくたって 雛月が
どこにいるかは 分かってる》
I didn't have to run.
I knew where Hinazuki would be.
《おそらく 母親から 虐待を受けている雛月は
家に帰りたくなくて
I suspected her mother was abusing her
and she didn't want to go home,
いつも 暗くなるまで
あの公園にいるんだ》
so she hung out at that park
until it got dark.
《俺は ただ
変な女って思ってたっけ》
Did I just think she was weird before?
≪雛月！
Hinazuki!
(雛月)藤沼…｡
何してんの？ こんなとこで｡
Fujinuma, what are you doing here?
俺のせりふだろ それ｡
友達になりたいって言っただろ｡
That's my line.
I told you. I wanna be friends.
人殺しは できないけど…｡
冗談に決まってるべさ｡
Although I can't kill anybody...
I was obviously kidding.
《うわっ…｡ 俺の苦手なタイプ》
It's hard for me to handle this type.
藤沼ってさ
何か ふりをしてるでしょ？
Fujinuma, you're pretending, aren't you?
えっ？
笑ってるふり｡
Pretending to smile...
優しいふり｡ 心配しているふり…｡
別に 悪いことだって思わないよ｡
Pretending to be nice...
Pretending to be worried...
I don't think that's a bad thing.
人のこと 言えないけど
藤沼の顔が見えない｡
And I'm not one to talk.
But I can't see you, Fujinuma.
そのとおりだと思うよ｡
俺は 演じてる｡
I think you're right.
I'm "performing."
人に好かれたい…
友達が欲しい…
I want people to like me.
I want to have friends.
人と接するのが苦手な自分に
何ができるって考えたら…
But I'm socially inept,
so when I thought,
"What can I do to help myself?"
the answer I got was,
俺の方が みんなのことを
好きになろうって思ったんだ｡
"Let's try liking everyone."
そしたら
演じるのが 少し楽になった｡
That made it a little easier to perform.
うん｡ 私も演じているうちに
本当になる気がするよ｡
Yeah.
While I'm performing, it feels like
it'll become real somewhere along the line.
(愛梨)《口に出して言ってるうちに
本当になる気がする》
I feel like if you say
the words over and over,
it'll actually happen
somewhere along the line.
《懐かしいと感じた
愛梨の言葉と同じ？》
Is it the same thing that Airi said,
which feels so long ago?
《みんな 何かを手に入れるために
我慢して 努力して スキルを身に付ける》
To get what you want,
you put up with something,
make an effort, learn a skill,
and inspire yourself.
《自分を奮い立たせて…》 《雛月も
そうなんじゃないか？ 今 きっと 耐えてる》
Is that how it is with Hinazuki too?
Right now... I can tell
she's enduring something.
《俺とは 真逆で
無関心を装ってる》
Just the opposite of me,
she's pretending to be indifferent.
《何も感じない自分を
演じようとしている》
She's acting as if she feels nothing.
《でも たかが 10歳の女の子が
そんなに強いわけない》
But a ten-year-old girl
just isn't that strong.
雛月 これ もらってくれる？
えっ？
Hinazuki. Would you accept this?
バースデーパーティーやるんだ｡
来てよ｡
BIRTHDAY PARTY
SATORU FUJINUMA
I'm having a birthday.
I want you to come.
わ… 私が行ってもいいの？
Y-You're inviting me?
他にも
人 いっぱい来るんでしょ？
There'll be a lot of other people, right?
まだ 分かんない｡ 最初に
雛月に渡そうって 決めてたから｡
I don't know yet.
I decided to give you the first invitation.
３月２日だから｡
えっ？
It's on March 2nd.
You will come, won't you?
来てくれるよね？
あっ うん…｡
Sure.
藤沼
手 冷たくない？
Fujinuma, aren't your hands cold?
ああ… まあ 冷たいけど｡
Oh. Yeah, they are, actually...
手袋 どっかに
置き忘れちゃったみたいなんだ｡
I think I left my gloves somewhere.
えっ… あっ…｡
《おい 29歳 しっかりしろ｡
何 照れてんだよ》
Hey. You're 29 years old.
Get a hold of yourself.
What are you embarrassed about?
藤沼 もう いいよ｡
あっ…｡
Fujinuma...
That's enough.
ヘヘヘッ｡
俺の方が 少し 手 おっきいね｡
My hand's a little bigger than yours, huh?
バカなの？
Are you stupid?
でもさ最近の藤沼は 少し 話しやすい｡
But still...
it's kind of easy to talk
to you these days, Fujinuma.
《まあ…》
Well...
雛月に 嘘をつかないって
決めたからな｡
That's because
I decided not to lie to you.
《声に出てた…》
I just said that out loud.
ひ… 雛月！
したっけ！ また あしたな！
H-Hinazuki!
I'll see you tomorrow!
《あいつも 手袋してなかったな》
She didn't have gloves either.
《ここが 18年前
雛月が 最後に目撃された場所》
This is the last place
I saw Hinazuki 18 years ago.
《遺体が見つかるのは
雪が解けた後だったはず》
Her body was found
after the snow melted.
GIRL
ISOLATION
DISAPPEARANCE
ABDUCT
DEAD
こんな公園で 雛月を
独りぼっちにさせない… 俺は｡
I won't let Hinazuki be alone in this park.
I...
HINAZUKI
《俺は 未来を変えたい》
I want to change the future!